# About Me

As a former teacher turned web developer, I bring a unique set of skills and experiences to each of my web development projects. My background in education has taught me the importance of user-centered designs, collaboration with colleagues, clear communication with clients, and intuitive design. My philosophy is that a well-designed website should not only teach users about a product or company, but spark their curiosity.

# **Technologies**

- HTML / CSS/ Javascript
- Node.js
- Typescript
- React
- Python
- Tailwind CSS
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- SQL
- MySQL
- PHP
- Git

## Other Skills

- Customer service
- Agile / Scrum
- Team collaboration
- Github / Bitbucket
- Laravel

# Work History

#### Personal Banker - First Bank (July 2024 - current)

Providing customer service, giving information about products, maintaining client relationships, and completing transactions.

#### Web Developer - Curiode (January 2024 - current)

Completing web development projects for clients, focusing on creating and optimizing websites for clients. Handling coding tasks such as building layouts, improving site performance, and ensuring responsiveness.

### Lead Teacher - Children's Courtyard (October 2023 - July 2024)

Overseeing classroom activities, providing educational instruction, and fostering a positive learning environment for children. Developing and implementing lesson plans.

#### Lead Teacher - Little Faces Childcare (May 2017 - October 2023)

Leading a team of educators in creating a nurturing environment for young children.

## Education

### University of Denver (2024 - current)

Currently enrolled in the University of Denver's Full Stack Coding Bootcamp to expand my coding knowledge.

### Western Carolina University (2018 - 2020)

Studied Early Childhood Education

#### Mars Hill University (2011 - 2015)

B.A. in Elementary Education